發現。
立法會主席。
在年2016至017。
我會 now report the conclusions and recommendations on the chapter funding of universities by UGC.
委員會對這些回覆滿意，並決定無需要公開聽證會討論這些章節。
regarding the issues relating to the research grants committee (RGC) raised in Chapter 6 of the director of audits report.
我們會像要借這個機會表達我們對局和部門提供詳細回覆我們問題的感謝。
財政年，行政院的經常性開支在教育上 amounted to 74.7 billion，係最大的開支領域。
The committee has concluded a visit to the council and received a detailed briefing on the council's mechanisms to assess research proposals and to avoid conflict of interest of its member.
on behalf of the committee, I would like to extend my heartfelt thanks to the Research Grants Council, the RGC, and its secretariat for arranging such a useful briefing to enhance members' understanding.
這些章節是基金會大學由大學基金委員會（UGC）撥款，以及公屋維修及安全改善。
鉛在飲用水、在一些公共租賃屋苑中，委員會決定延遲表決本章的報告，以給我們更多時間考慮這些問題。
Out of the 10 chapters covered by the Director of Audits report number 67, PAC has decided to hold hearings on two chapters that contain more serious allegations of irregularities or shortcomings.
委員會也研究了其他七章，由問詢有關的部處提供書面回覆，就成員提出的問題，就如何處理審計總署報告第67號所提出的不足之處。
石乃謙石乃謙議員就政府帳目委員會第六十七號報告書向本會發言。石乃謙議員，Thank you, Mr. President. On behalf of the Public Accounts Committee (PAC), I have the honour to table our report number sixty-seven today.
議員議案根據適宜及通則條例。
And be transparent and accountable in using public resources.
委員會 urge the UGC to rectify the irregularities and inadequacies expeditiously.
Bureau should continue to monitor the UGC-funded university programme performance on internationalisation.
Out of this sum, around 18 billion was earmarked for grants and reimbursement provided to the eight universities funded by UGC.
Lastly, but not the least, I like to thank wholeheartedly the Secretariat of PAC for their unfailing support. Thank you, Mr. President.
given the substantial amount of resources involved in tertiary education, UGC and UGC Secretariat should exercise good governance.
The committee expresses grave concern and dissatisfaction, and finds it unacceptable that UGC's management of conflicts of interest.
作為一個例子，是那26個註冊利益關係表的成員，於UGC和品質保證委員會的UGC，被發現遺失。
委員也表達深切關切和滿意，關於缺乏有用的統計數據來評估國際化大學的效益。
委員會同意國際化大學的重要性，並要求UGC和教育局編製相關統計，以評估現行政策的經濟效益。
UGC和教育 bureau have not complied. They have not compiled statistic on whether non-local graduates of UGC funded undergraduate and postgraduate programme would study or work in Hong Kong.
委員會的報告今日 covers our conclusions and recommendations on the chapter funding of universities by UGC only. For the chapter on the maintenance of public rental housing, as well as information have been provided by the witnesses on the issue relating to excess.
Furthermore, UGC and the Education Bureau should also regularly review whether the present mix of non-local students and public grants to university have achieved the intended objectives of internationalisation. UGC and the Education
lastly, Mr. President, I wish to recall my appreciation of the contribution made by members of the committee. Our gratitude also goes to witnesses who attended the hearings held by the committee. I would like to express our gratitude to the director of audit and his colleagues for their support.